

Experienced call center agent with a team orientated personality, strong communication & listening skills. A natural flair for customer service with a friendly, empathetic manner.

An outgoing character with a calm, positive temperament.

Thrives in a fast paced environment and enthusiastic to begin a new challenge.

EXPERIENCE:

MANAGERS ASSISTANT

PIKES IBIZA

APRIL 2022-OCTOBER 2022

- Team orientated role, providing support to management, the events team, hosting & artist liason.
- Multitasking as a dedicated team support, ensuring the highest standard of guest experience. Reporting and responding to any guest complaints and issues.
- Demostrating a professional & positive attitude, hosting high profile guests and elegantly representing the vision of an iconic, luxury boutique hotel & nightclub

HOST & CUSTOMER SERVICE AERO AIRLINE APRIL 2020-OCTOBER 2021

- Ground staff at Ibiza's private airport lounge; creating a welcoming and calming reception, hosting clients travelling on first class jets. Proactively responding to customer queries and complaints.
- Communicating through multiple airline channels, checking passenger documents, administrating tickets, correctly recording detailed data and ensuring boarder safety imformation.
- Adhearing to strict policies and company image guidelines with meticulous time mangement skills.

SALES ASSOCIATE

PEACH BOUTIQUE

APRIL 2018-OCTOBER 2020

• Engaging with customers to find products to fit their needs. Ensuring a smooth sales process, explaining clear and precise product & brand knowledge, with an enthusiastic, encouraging attitude. Being motivated and trustworthy, exceeding sales targets.

SALES REPRESENTATIVE & ACCOUNT MANAGER

WOWCHER

JANUARY 2017 - MARCH 2018

- Identifying leads, direct sales, pitching services and nurturing customer and business relationships.
- Upselling to meet sales targets and customer retention. Processing payments and organising appointments to increase sales revenue.
- Managing multiple CRM Systems, creating online content, keeping detailed and accurate records, managing call time effectively.

EDUCATION

BA HONS:

MARKETING MANAGEMENT

Manchester Metropolitan University 2011-2015

ADVANCED NATIONAL DIPOMA TRAVEL & TOURISM

Llandrillo College Wales 2007-2011

SKILLS

- Excellent written & verbal command of the English language
- professional telephone manner
- Computer literacy
- Project Management & multitasking abilities
- Strong interpersonal communication skills
- Demonstratable customer service excellence